A Guide to the Woodbine Cemetery Records, ca. 1830-2006 (bulk 1940-2000): SC 0236
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Woodbine Cemetery Records
ca. 1830-2006 (bulk 1940-2006)
Special Collections, James Madison University
Woodbine Cemetery
SC 0236
24.77 cubic feet; 70 boxes, 6 flat files
The Woodbine Cemetery Records, ca.1830-2006, consist of materials relating to the operation of Woodbine Cemetery, in Harrisonburg, Virginia. The collection includes a wide array of financial and commercial materials, including receipt books and loose receipts, account books, checks, ledgers, bank statements, board minutes and reports, customer correspondence, insurance information, maps, and other materials produced during the course of business over approximately the past 150 years.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Parts of the collection are restricted, due to the presence of personally identifying information. Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection. Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the James Madison University Special Collections Library to use this collection.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated by Charlie Chenault, Woodbine Cemetery Board of Trustees, Secretary/Treasurer, on August 27, 2015.
Administrative History
Woodbine Cemetery Company was founded on March 19, 1850 by the Virginia General Assembly, as a non-denominational burial ground in Harrisonburg, Virginia. The first land for the cemetery was purchased seven months later, on October 11, 1850, from Harrisonburg's first mayor, Isaac Hardesty, who sold 2½ acres to the cemetery company. It has continued to expand in size over the years, and the current grounds cover about 18 acres. Woodbine Cemetery contains roughly 11,550 burial plots with approximately 9,000 interred.
Soon after the Civil War, the cemetery created an area dedicated to Confederate soldiers and veterans. This section was originally maintained by the Ladies Memorial Association, founded in 1868 with the charge of caring for the graves of Confederate soldiers buried in Rockingham County. The Ladies Memorial Association erected a soldiers monument in 1876, and in 1899 with the aid of the Turner Ashby Chapter of the United Daughters of the Confederacy, replaced all wooden head boards with white marble stones. The section was expanded in 1886, when Samuel Shacklett donated a 5 acre-plot, containing land likely already in use as a Confederate cemetery. There are now over 200 Confederate soldier or veterans buried there, representing states of Virginia, North Carolina, Maryland, Louisiana, Alabama, South Carolina, Georgia, Missouri, and Tennessee. The cemetery also contains area known as "Little Arlington," dedicated to those who served in World War I and World War II.
The Community Mausoleum was erected in 1926, though there are no records of incorporation until 1936, when it was incorporated as the "Communal Mausoleum Crypt Owners, Inc." In February 2006, the mausoleum merged with Woodbine Cemetery Company.
According to a Woodbine Board of Trustees report dated April 2, 1853, the original cemetery contained plots designated for African Americans, stating, "…in the rear plats have already been appropriated to single interments, and likewise for the use of colored persons." According to Nelson J. Liskey's, "History of Woodbine Cemetery," in 1969, the board adopted a policy that "no restrictions as to race would be applicable to lot purchasers."
Superintendents of Woodbine Cemetery include, but are not limited to, the following individuals: John Foster (1851), J.P. Hyde (1863), J.E. Good (1880), Bowman Gilmer (1918-1958), Sherman Gilmer (1958-1981), David Schrock (1981-1992), Lisa Batchelder (1992-present).
Scope and Content
The Woodbine Cemetery Records, ca. 1830-2006, are comprised of materials related to the operation of Woodbine Cemetery, in Harrisonburg, Virginia. The collection includes a wide array of financial and commercial materials, including receipt books and loose receipts, account books, checks, ledgers, bank statements, board minutes and reports, customer correspondence, insurance information, maps, and other materials produced during the course of business, between the 1850s and 2006. This includes records relating to the management of the Woodbine Mausoleum, which existed as a separate entity until 2006, when it was acquired by Woodbine Cemetery.
Due to the lengthy time period covered, the materials were collected and organized by a variety of individuals, and completeness of the records varies. When possible, the original order and naming conventions were retained. The material relates almost exclusively to Woodbine Cemetery in Harrisonburg VA, though some of the ephemera relates to other cemeteries as well.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in six series:
Series 1: Financial Files, ca. 1840-2006 (bulk 1890-2006)
Series 2: Administrative Files, 1853-2002
Series 3: Business Records, 1898-2006
Series 4: Mausoleum Records, 1924-2006
Series 5: Ephemera, 1985-2000
Series 6: Maps, 1913-1966
Broadly speaking, each series is arranged first by the type of material, and then chronologically within these broader categories. Exceptions to this arrangement were made in order to pay respects to the original order, as well as when precise dates could not be readily determined.
Separated Materials
A copy of the book, "Beautiful Thornrose," edited by Arista Hoge (Staunton, VA: Press of the McClure Co., 1914), was separated from the collection, and is housed in Special Collections Monographs, F234.S8 B4 1914.
Bibliography
Liskey, Nelson J. "History of Woodbine Cemetery," Harrisonburg, VA. 1998.
"About Woodbine." Woodbine Cemetery. http://woodbinecemetery.org/about-woodbine/ (Accessed September 19, 2018).
Moore, Robert H. "The Woodbine Cemetery." Historical Marker Database, February 26, 2009. https://www.hmdb.org/marker.asp?marker=16486 (Accessed September 19, 2018).
Index Terms
Subjects:
Cemeteries -- Virginia -- Rockingham County; Harrisonburg (Va.) -- History; Harrisonburg (Va.) -- Genealogy; Rockingham County (Va.) -- History; Rockingham County (Va.) -- Genealogy; Cemeteries -- Virginia -- Harrisonburg
Genre and Form Terms:
Financial Records; Receipts (financial records); Minutes (administrative records); Maps (documents); Plats (maps); Checks (bank checks); Directories; Ledgers (account books); Administrative reports; Letters (correspondence); Deeds
- Series 1: Financial Files, ca. 1840-2006
  Scope and Contents
  Financial Files, ca. 1840-2006, is comprised of financial documents of various types. These include receipts for materials purchased by the cemetery for operations, including hardware, materials, landscaping services, and other expenses relating to the day-to-day care of the cemetery grounds and buildings. Cemetery account books, receipt books, and ledgers track the income and expenditures of the Cemetery, including payments made to the cemetery for the one-time purchase of plots and ongoing income from perpetual care plots. Additional information includes cemetery tax documents are returns, employee payment and salary information, banking documents (including deposit slips and account statements), donor pledges, and other related documents directly impacting the financial affairs of Woodbine cemetery. Certain folder within this series are restricted, due to the presence of personally identifying information.
  - Receipt Book, August 1942-December 1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, January 1944 – April 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, April 1944-February 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, February 1945-June 1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, June 1945-March 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, March 1946-March 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, March 1947-December 1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, January 1948-September 1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, September 1948-July 1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, July 1949-June 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, June 1950-February 1951 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, February 1951-May 1951 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, May 1951-January 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, January 1952-May 1952 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, May 1952-November 1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, November 1952-March 1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, March 1953-September 1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, September 1953-March 1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, March 1954-October 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, October 1954-March 1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, March 1955-May 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, May 1956-January 1957 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, January 1957-May 1957 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, May 1957 – February 1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, February 1958-October 1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, October 1958-February 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, February 1959-February 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, February 1960-September 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, September 1960-March 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, March 1961-January 1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, January 1962-November 1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, November 1962-May 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, May 1963-February 1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, February 1964-January 1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, January 1965-November 1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, November 1965-June 1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, July 1966-February 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, February 1967-January 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, January 1968-October 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, October 1968-May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, May 1969-February 1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, February 1970-January 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, January 1971-December 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, December 1971-July 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, July 1972-February 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, March 1973-January 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, January 1974-Oct 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, Oct 1974-April 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, April. 1975-January 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, January 1976-January 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, January 1977-November. 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, November 1977-July 1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, July 1978-April 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, April 1979-January 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Receipt Book, February 1980-January 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, January 1981-November 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, November 1981-September 1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, September 1982-July 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, July 1983-June 1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, June 1984-May 1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, May 1985-April 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, April 1986-March 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, March 1987-April 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, April 1988-March 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Receipt Book, March 1989-Oct 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Receipt Book, Oct 1990-August 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Receipt Book, August. 1992-January 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Receipt Book, April 1999-February 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Receipt Book, March 2001-June 2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Checking Book, November 1926-June 1937 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Checking Book, December 1936, June 1937-September 1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Checking Book, September 1945-July 1950 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Checking Book, July 1952-August 1954 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Checking Book, August 1954-September 1958 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Checking Book, September 1958-April 1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Checking Book, April 1965-July 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Checking Book, July 1969-March 1973 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Checking Book, March. 1973-September 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Checking Book, September 1975-May 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Checking Book, May 1978-December 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Loose Check Receipts, 1950–1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Loose Checks, 1909–1943 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Loose Checks, 1943–1945 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Loose Checks, 1946–1954 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Loose Checks, 1955–1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Loose Checks, 1958–1966 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Loose Checks, 1967–1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Loose Checks, 1970–1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Loose Checks, 1978–1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Invoices and Receipts A-D, ca. 1890 – ca. 1950 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Invoices and Receipts E-F, ca. 1890 – ca. 1950 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Invoices and Receipts G, ca. 1890 – ca. 1950 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Invoices and Receipts H-M, ca. 1890 – ca. 1950 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Invoices and Receipts N-S, ca. 1890 – ca. 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Invoices and Receipts T-Z, ca. 1890 – ca. 1950 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Balance Sheets, 1901–1950 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Quarterly Interest Slips, 1967–1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - General Ledger Sheets, 1986–1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Deposit Slips, August 1942-December 1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Deposit Slips, January 1960-December 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Deposit Slips, January 1971-October 1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Account Information, 1981–1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Perpetual Care Account, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Interest Income, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - General Investments, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Bank Statements - Misc. Old Dominion, 1981–1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Dominion Bank Account, 1984 -1988 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Charge Slips, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Receipts, 1839–1880 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Account Books, 1912–1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Account Books, 1950–1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Year End Financial Reports, 1956–1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Year End Financial Reports, 1971–1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Year End Financial Reports, 1983–1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Perpetual Care Savings Statements, 1984–1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Payroll/Financial, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Payroll/Financial, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Investors Savings Bank Money Market, 1985–1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Investors Savings and Loan Association, Certificates of Deposit, 1984–1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - American Federal Certificate of Deposit, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Special Endowment Fund, 1982 – 1985 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Endowment Gifts – Lists of Donors, 1984–1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Deposits, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Park View Mennonite Church Budget, 1988–1989 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Brokerage Account, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - T. Rowe Price Investment, 1986 – 1987 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Tax Guides, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Financial Projections, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Reports on Disbursements and Receipts, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Tax Information, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Donor Pledge Cards, 1982–1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Annual Assessment, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Chevron, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - South Branch Valley National Bank, Certificates of Deposit, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Signet Bank Account Information, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Tax Information – Interest, 1985–1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Deeds, 1980–1991 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Jefferson National Bank, 1984–1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Consumer Use Tax, 1972, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Fiduciary Responsibility, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Deposit Slips, 1988–1989 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Payroll/Financial, 1989–1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Transaction Journals, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Ledger Sheets, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Federal Tax Deposit Coupon Book, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Employer Tax Guide, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Payroll/Financial, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Insurance Receipts, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - CD General Info, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - CD SBU National Bank, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - CD Signet Bank, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - CD Investors (T-5) Matured 1/27/1989, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - CD Investors (T-6) Matured 5/25/1989, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - CD Crestar Matured 11/13/1989, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - CD Crestar, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - CD – First American Bank, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Checkbook Stubs, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Bank Statements – Market Plus, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Bank Statements, Checking, 1989–1990 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Auditor Files, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia Electric Stock Purchases, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Tax Forms, etc. (Federal), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1993–1997 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Transaction Sheets, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Woodbine Income and Expense Charts, 1992–1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Tax Forms, etc. (Federal), 1995 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Tax Forms, etc. (Federal), 1996 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Tax Forms, etc. (Federal), 1997 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Tax Forms, etc. (Federal), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Tax Forms, etc. (Federal), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Portfolio Reports, May 1999 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Employee Wage Sheets, 1994–2002 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - VA Tax Forms, 1996–2001 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Federal Tax Forms, 1997–2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Tax Form 941, 1998–2002 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1998–2001 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Wages and Holdings, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Accountant Information, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Legal Bills, 2001–2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - VA State Annual Report, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Check Stubs, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Cancelled Checks, 2000, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Account Summary First Union, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Woodbine Est. Portfolio Value Graph, 1994–2002 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 2003–2004 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Deeds and Receipts, 1928–1934 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Confederate Memorial Funds, 1979–1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1981–1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Deposit Slips, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Tax Information, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Amortization Schedule, 1968–1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Payroll, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Payroll, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Payroll, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - General Ledger Sheets, 1928–1946 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Ledger Sheets, 1946–1956 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Ledger Sheets, 1940–1984 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Ledger Sheets, 1984–1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Ledger Sheets, 1942–1965 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Financial Receipt Books, 1914–1946 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - General Ledger Sheets, 1960–1966 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - General Ledger Sheets, 1966–1970 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - General Ledger Sheets, 1970–1976 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - General Ledger Sheets, 1977–1985 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Woodbine General Ledger, 1927–1941 (Box OV 1)
  - Woodbine Cash Ledger, August 1942-December 1946 (Box OV 2)
  - Woodbine Cash Ledger, January 1947-April 1951 (Box OV 2)
  - Woodbine Cash Ledger, May 1951-June 1955 (Box OV 2)
  - Woodbine Cash Ledger, July 1955-January 1960 (Box OV 2)
- Series 2: Administrative Files, ca. 1830-2002
  Administrative Files, ca. 1830-2002, is comprised of documents which record the information used to manage the cemetery. As such, it contains reports and minutes compiled by the cemetery's various treasurers and presidents over the years, information relating to board meetings, insurance policy papers, and other similar documents created in the course of running the business.
  - Board Reports, 1853, 1907 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Notes, 1990–1995 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Persons Buried in Woodbine, 1850–2000 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - ByLaws, 1902–1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Woodbine Insurance Papers, 1999–2002 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Trustees, 1951–1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Items Used at Woodbine Office, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Files, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Grogg-Sparks Lot 653, 2001–2002 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Groundskeeper Job Description, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Map and Plot Layouts, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Liability Insurance Policy, 1987–1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Worker's Compensation, 1986–1988 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Fidelity Bond Insurance, 1987–1988 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - CPA – General and Miscellaneous Info, 1983–1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1985–1987 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Library Minute Books Agreement, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1984–1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Woodbine Insurance Papers - Shank, 1978–1987 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Woodbine Insurance Papers - Mumaw, 1969–1984 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Woodbine Insurance Papers - Offenbacker, 1982–1992 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Woodbine Insurance Papers - Hottinger, 1983–1986 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Woodbine Insurance Papers - Texiere, 1983–1989 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Woodbine Insurance Papers - Ludholtz, 1981–1987 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Unemployment Compensation and Occupational Safety, 1966–1974 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Form 1099, 1964, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Union Bank Letter, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Wheat Securities, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Confederate Monument, 2001-06-22T00:00:00.000 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Columbarium Information, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Cemetery Association, 1967–1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report of the Superintendent, 1981–1983 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Management Reports, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Spreadsheets and Management Reports, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Leadership Models/Organization, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Society for Non-Profit Organizations (SFNO) Information, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Cemetery Survey, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - State Corporate Commissions, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Insurance Papers, 1982–1991 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Insurance, 1990–1991 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Truck, 1986–1989 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - David Shrock's "Cash Flow Analysis" and "Current Investment Information", 1991–1992 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Quarterly Management Reports and Minutes, 1982–1987 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1988–1991 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1992–1996 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1997–2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Notes, 1940–1944 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Notes, 1945–1949 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Notes, 1950–1959 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1961–1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Notes, 1985–1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Woodbine Trustee Matters and Photographs, 1959–1982 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Items From Bank Vault, 1851–1974 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - President's Records, 1968–1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - President's Records, 1984–1987 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Woodbine Insurance Papers - See, 1986–1989 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Day Books, ca. 1830 – ca. 1950 (Box 66, Folder 5)